-What I've read and heard, I don't trust the vaccines at all.
I also have some underlying diseases that I am more afraid of the vaccine than I am too covid.
-You haven't had covid or?
-No, not what I know.
-But you are not afraid to get covid here today considering that it is so high spread?
-No, I'm not actually.
I feel pretty confident in what is anyway.
I think it's a lot of scare.
Okay, it's a very serious illness anyway for those affected.
Many people have also died with underlying diseases and that is what I have.
-We have no pandemic, it is only statistics that they themselves have created.
-You mean the virus doesn't exist at all?
-There is not Covid-19 in that way.
It is a common flu or cold which has nothing to do with any virus.
It has to do with the body's slag products wanting out of the body on what you have eaten and taken in through water and air throughout the year.
When they arrived here you saw a little.
-There are very masked people also with Bengals and stuff.
I don't know, it doesn't feel like everyone here to demonstrate against the vaccine pass either.
-It feels like everyone is not here on the same agenda, but it feels like some have a different view of this.
Giants!
-Yes to freedom, yes to freedom!
-You are one of the last left here now that the demonstration is running out and you stand here with your poster that says "Warning for vaccination pass".
Tell me more, what do you think?
I think our freedoms are taken away from us, especially our children.
This is probably not just about health, but it is about it being like China dictatorship this feels like.
We must stand up now when we can, before it becomes completely dictatorship.
-What do you think about the vaccine, is it toxic or?